And you don't want
to buy too much
because you could financially
overextend yourself and you
don't want to buy
too little because then
you can't serve all
the revenue And so
that's where the kind
of economic and financial
is But you are
involved in that building
data centers you're vast
fortunes you've got the
deals with Nvidia Do
you worry that that's
going to come back
and you So we
have some advantages in
this There's a stability
to business that there
is not to consumer
right Consumer is very
fickle Enterprise purchasing
predictions are predictable Also
enterprise tends to have
better margins The margin
is basically how much
buffer you have between
buying too little and
buying too much what
you have to pay
for and what you
have to support in
revenue So we have
a of here but
I won't deny that
there is some inherent
risk in all
of the to this
process